var Questions = [
    {
      question : `What is Terry's favourite food?
      a. Milk
      b. Yogurt
      c. Protein powder
      \n`,
      answer : "b"
  },
  
  {
    question : `Which precinct of the NYPD is Brooklyn 99 set in?
    a. 11
    b. 99
    c. 22
    \n`,
    answer : "b"
  },
  
  {
    question : `Which character does Joe Lo Truglio play?
    a. Pimento
    b. Jake Peralta
    c. Charles Boyle
    \n`,
    answer : "c"
  },
  
  {
    question : `Who plays violin at Jake and Amy's wedding?
    a. Mleponos
    b. Boyle
    c. Scully
    \n`,
    answer : "a"
  },
  
  {
    question : `What is Nutriboom?
    a. New drug
    b. Nickname for Terry
    c. A pyramid scheme
    \n`,
    answer : "c"
  },
  
  {
    question : `Which two character's parents get married?
    a. Boyle's and Linetti's
    b. Santiago's and Diaz's
    c. Boyle's and Diaz's
    \n`,
    answer : "a"
  },
  
  {
    question : `What does Jake attempt to steal from Holt in the first Halloween episode?
    a. Cummerband
    b. Watch
    c. Shoe
    \n`, 
    answer : "b"
  },
  
  {
    question : `What is the Vulture's real name?
    a. Pembroke
    b. Judy
    c. Pimento
    \n`,
    answer : "a"
  },
  
  {
    question : `What drug does the team try to take down in season two?
    a. SillyPowder
    b. GigglePig
    c. White
    \n`,
    answer : "b"
  },
  
  {
    question : `What did Holt do with Wuntch when they met Mitchelle Obama?
    a. Pushed Wuntch into Mitchelle Omaba
    b. Made a dig of Wuntch
    c. Spoke nonsense about Wuntch
    \n`,
    answer : "a"
  }
  
  ];
  
  module.exports = Questions;
  